Register of the Stanford University Institute of Hispanic American and Luso-Brazilian Studies Collection, 1954-1965
Hoover Institution Archives
- February 1961
  - Puerto Rico
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes) (Box 325.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes) (Box 326.)
- March 1961
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 326.)
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 327.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 328.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba (6 envelopes, one containing Avance) (Box 329.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras (Box 330.)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes) (Box 331.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies (Box 332.)
  - International, (4 envelopes)
- April 1961
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 332.)
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 333.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Bolivia (Box 334.)
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes) (Box 335.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (6 envelopes) (Box 336.)
  - Cuba (Box 337.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico (Box 338.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay (Box 339.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes) (Box 340.)
- May 1961
  - Argentina, (5 envelopes) (Box 340.)
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 341.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 342.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia (5 envelopes, one containing Diario las Americas, one containing El Tiempo: May 1-13, another El Tiempo: May 14-26, and another El Tiempo: May 27-31)
  - Costa Rica (Box 343.)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 344.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti (Box 345.)
  - Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Portugal (Box 346.)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West-Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (4 envelopes) (Box 347.)
- June 1961
  - Argentina, (6 envelopes) (Box 347.)
  - Argentina (Box 348.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes) (Box 349.)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 350.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (3 envelopes) (Box 351.)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala, (2 envelopes)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico (Box 352.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 353.)
  - West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (3 envelopes) (Box 354.)
- July 1961
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 354.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 355.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes) (Box 356.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 357.)
  - Dominican Republic, (3 envelopes)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 358.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico
  - Puerto Rico (Box 359.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
- August 1961
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 360.)
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil (3 envelopes, 2 of which are August-September
  - Brazil, (5 envelopes) (Box 361.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (2 envelopes) (Box 362.)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 363.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama (Box 364.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes) (Box 365.)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (5 envelopes)
- September 1961
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 366.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (5 envelopes) (Box 367.)
  - Brazil, (5 envelopes) (Box 368.)
  - Central America (Box 369.)
  - Chile, (4 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica (Box 370.)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 371.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (5 envelopes) (Box 372.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - West Indies
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras
  - French West Indies (Box 373.)
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes)
- October 1961
  - Argentina, (5 envelopes) (Box 373.)
  - Bolivia (Box 374.)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Central America
  - Chile
  - Chile (Box 375.)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes) (Box 376.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico (4 envelopes, one containing material of Sept. 27-30) (Box 377.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (4 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 378.)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 379.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes)
- November 1961
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 380.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes) (Box 381.)
  - Central America
  - Chile
  - Chile (Box 382.)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba (Box 383.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 384.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru (Box 385.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain (Box 386.)
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 387.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes) (Box 388.)
- December 1961
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 388.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 389.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes) (Box 390.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes) (Box 391.)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes) (Box 392.)
  - Portugal, (3 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes) (Box 393.)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes) (Box 394.)
  - Venezuela (5 envelopes, one containing Official Presidential Proclamations of 1961)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes) (Box 395.)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (5 envelopes)
- January 1962
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 396.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 397.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes) (Box 398.)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Dominican Republic (Box 399.)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras (2 envelopes, one containing Jan-Feb)
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico (Box 400.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Peru (Box 401.)
  - Portugal, (3 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes) (Box 402.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
  - International (10 envelopes, 1 of which contains material concerning Sino-Cuban relations, 1 containing The Vision, 1 containing the Shoumatoff Papers, 2 which contain scripts of Contemporary Revolution in Latin America produced by University of Florida, and 1 which contains comments on the Punta del Este Conference) (Box 403.)
- February 1962
  - Argentina (Box 404.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes) (Box 405.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes) (Box 406.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes) (Box 407.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 408.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Peru, (2 envelopes) (Box 409.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain (Box 410.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes) (Box 411.)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (5 envelopes)
- March 1962
  - Argentina (6 envelopes) one containing economic material (Box 412.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes) (Box 413.)
  - Central America
  - Chili, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (7 envelopes) (Box 414.)
  - Colombia (Box 415.)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 416.)
  - Ecuador, (4 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala, (2 envelopes)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 417.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru, (2 envelopes) (Box 418.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Uruguay (Box 419.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes) (Box 420.)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes)
- April 1962
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 421.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil
  - Brazil, (4 envelopes) (Box 422.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (3 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes) (Box 423.)
  - Costa Rica, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Cuba (Box 424.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (4 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Guatemala (Box 425.)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (5 envelopes) (Box 426.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes) (Box 427.)
  - Uruguay
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 428.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (4 envelopes) (Box 429.)
- May 1962
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 429.)
  - Argentina (containing economic section) (Box 430.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 431.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (4 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 432.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 433.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Peru, (4 envelopes) (Box 434.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain, (3 envelopes) (Box 435.)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 436.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 437.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes) (Box 438.)
- June 1962
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 438.)
  - Argentina (4 envelopes, one containing economic material) (Box 439.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 440.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba (Box 441.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala, (2 envelopes)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico (5 envelopes, 2 containing June-July) (Box 442.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (8 envelopes) (Box 443.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes) (Box 444.)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain, (3 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (4 envelopes) (Box 445.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 446.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras (Box 447.)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (4 envelopes)
- July 1962
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 447.)
  - Argentina (3 envelopes, one containing economic material) (Box 448.)
  - Bolivia, (3 envelopes)
  - Brazil
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes) (Box 449.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (3 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia (Box 450.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes) (Box 451.)
  - Ecuador, (3 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala, (2 envelopes)
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico (3 envelopes, 2 containing Excelsior July 1-15, one containing Excelsior July 16-30)
  - Mexico (3 envelopes, one containing Excelsior July 16-30) (Box 452.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru, (8 envelopes) (Box 453.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes) (Box 454.)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes) (Box 455.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 456.)
  - Venezuela (Box 457.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (2 envelopes) (Box 458.)
- August 1962
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 458.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 459.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 460.)
  - Cuba (Box 461.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 462.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru, (5 envelopes) (Box 463.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (3 envelopes) (Box 464.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Uruguay, (2 envelopes) (Box 465.)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (4 envelopes) (Box 466.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (3 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (6 envelopes) (Box 467.)
- September 1962
  - Argentina, (5 envelopes) (Box 468.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 469.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (3 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia (Box 470.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 471.)
  - Cuba (Box 472.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras (Box 473.)
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes) (Box 474.)
  - Panama, (2 envelopes)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Peru, (3 envelopes) (Box 475.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes) (Box 476.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (3 envelopes) (Box 477.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes) (Box 478.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (5 envelopes) (Box 479.)
- October 1962
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 480.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 481.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (3 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (7 envelopes) (Box 482.)
  - Costa Rica (Box 483.)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes) (Box 484.)
  - Cuba, (6 envelopes) (Box 485.)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 486.)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 487.)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (3 envelopes) (Box 488.)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama (Box 489.)
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (4 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Portugal (Box 490.)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain (Box 491.)
  - Uruguay, (5 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (7 envelopes) (Box 492.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 493.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- November 1962
  - Argentina, (4 envelopes) (Box 494.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Brazil (Box 495.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (4 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (6 envelopes) (Box 496.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 497.)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 498.)
  - Cuba, (7 envelopes) (Box 499.)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 500.)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 501.)
  - Nicaragua
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru
  - Peru, (3 envelopes) (Box 502.)
  - Portugal
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes) (Box 503.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (8 envelopes) (Box 504.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes) (Box 505.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies (Box 506.)
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- December 1962
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 506.)
  - Bolivia
  - Bolivia (Box 507.)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile
  - Chile (Box 508.)
  - Colombia, (6 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica (Box 509.)
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes) (Box 510.)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 511.)
  - Dominican Republic (3 envelopes, one of which contains Election Material)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico (5 envelopes, one containing Excelsior Dec. 1-15, two containing Excelsior Dec. 16-31) (Box 512.)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes) (Box 513.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (3 envelopes)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes) (Box 514.)
  - Puerto Rico, (2 envelopes)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes) (Box 515.)
  - Uruguay, (4 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (6 envelopes) (Box 516.)
  - Venezuela, (2 envelopes) (Box 517.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- January 1963
  - Argentina (Box 517.)
  - Argentina (Box 518.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (3 envelopes)
  - Central America and Panama (Box 519.)
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (5 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (3 envelopes) (Box 520.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes)
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes) (Box 521.)
  - Dominican Republic (Box 522.)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador, (2 envelopes)
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico, (4 envelopes) (Box 523.)
  - Mexico (Box 524.)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (2 envelopes)
  - Peru, (4 envelopes) (Box 525.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, Virgin Islands
  - Puerto Rico, Virgin Islands, (2 envelopes) (Box 526.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay
  - Uruguay, (4 envelopes) (Box 527.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes) (Box 528.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (2 envelopes) (Box 529.)
- February 1963
  - Argentina, (3 envelopes) (Box 529.)
  - Bolivia
  - Brazil
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 530.)
  - Central America and Panama
  - Chile, (4 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (2 envelopes)
  - Colombia, (5 envelopes) (Box 531.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 532.)
  - Cuba, (5 envelopes) (Box 533.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes) (Box 534.)
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico
  - Mexico (6 envelopes) one containing Excelsior Feb. 1-10 except 6 & 7, another containing Excelsior Feb. 11-20 except 12, another containing La Tribuna Feb. 1-5, 7, 29, and another containing El Imparcial Feb. 6-10, 20-23, 25-28.) (Box 535.)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes) (Box 536.)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (4 envelopes)
  - Portugal
  - Portugal (Box 537.)
  - Puerto Rico, Virgin Islands, (4 envelopes)
  - Spain
  - Spain, (2 envelopes) (Box 538.)
  - Uruguay, (4 envelopes)
  - Venezuela
  - Venezuela, (5 envelopes) (Box 539.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes) (Box 540.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana, British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - Other Islands and British Honduras (Feb.-May)
  - Trinidad (Jan.-April)
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - International, (3 envelopes)
- March 1963
  - Argentina (Box 540.)
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 541.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil (Box 542.)
  - Central America, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile, (4 envelopes)
  - Colombia
  - Colombia, (5 envelopes) (Box 543.)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes) (Box 544.)
  - Cuba, (3 envelopes) (Box 545.)
  - Dominican Republic
  - Ecuador, (2 envelopes)
  - El Salvador (Box 546.)
  - Guatemala
  - Haiti
  - Honduras
  - Mexico, (5 envelopes)
  - Mexico, (2 envelopes) (Box 547.)
  - Nicaragua, (2 envelopes)
  - Panama
  - Paraguay
  - Peru, (4 envelopes) (Box 548.)
  - Portugal, (2 envelopes)
  - Puerto Rico, Virgin Islands, (4 envelopes) (Box 549.)
  - Spain, (2 envelopes)
  - Uruguay, (4 envelopes) (Box 550.)
  - Venezuela, (3 envelopes)
  - Venezuela, (6 envelopes) (Box 551.)
  - West Indies, British Guiana
  - British Honduras, (2 envelopes)
  - Trinidad (Box 552.)
  - West Indies - Jamaica
  - French West Indies
  - Netherlands West Indies
  - West Indies General, (2 envelopes)
  - International, (4 envelopes)
  - International (Box 553.)
- April 1963
  - Argentina, (2 envelopes) (Box 553.)
  - Bolivia, (2 envelopes)
  - Brazil
  - Brazil, (2 envelopes) (Box 554.)
  - Central America
  - Chile, (2 envelopes)
  - Chile (Box 555.)
  - Colombia, (6 envelopes)
  - Costa Rica
  - Cuba
  - Cuba, (4 envelopes) (Box 556.)
  - Cuba, (2 envelopes) (Box 557.)
  - Dominican Republic, (2 envelopes)